纽约北部
Shit.
糟糕
What the hell are you doing out here?
你到这儿来干什么?
I had to drive all night.
我开了一整夜的车
I'm hungover as shit.
我酒还没醒呢
And you're really starting to cut into my vacation time,
你在糟蹋我的假期时间
so can we go, please?
那我们可以走了吧?
We'll take my car. Come on.
坐我的车 走吧
I don't think so.
我不走
Why you making... why are you gonna make this difficult?
你为什么... 为什么老把事情弄得这么复杂?
What's difficult? He turns himself in. Then it's easy.
什么复杂了? 他自首去 然后一切就都很简单了
Turns himself in. Why would he do that?
自首 他自首干什么?
What exactly did he say I did?
他到底说我干什么了?
He didn't. He just said to come pick you up.
什么都没说 他只是让我过来接你
Nothing else? Nothing about Barcelona?
没别的了吗? 没提巴塞罗那那事?
No.
没有
Nothing about Dublin? Nothing about Paul?
没提都柏林? 也没提保罗那事?
Hi. Can I get you something?
嗨 你要点点什么?
- Need a minute?  - Y'all have beer?
- 还是等一会再点?  - 你这儿有啤酒吗?
No, I wish.
没有
Just a coffee. Black.
那就来杯咖啡吧 清咖啡
Okay, if you got something to say, say it.
好了 你有什么想说的 就赶紧说
Aaron...
Aaron啊...
Have you even seen him?
你见过他吧?
No.
没有
You're really not getting in the car, are you?
你真的不上车 是不是?
No.
不上
- Thank you.  - Have you got any...
- 谢谢  - 你有没有...
You need to get in the car, Mallory!
你现在就得上车 Mallory!
- You got a car? You got a car?  - What?
- 你有车吗? 你有车吗?  - 怎么了?
- Which one?  - This one.
- 哪一辆?  - 这辆
No, no, passenger side. Give me your keys.
不 不 你坐副驾驶 把车钥匙给我
- Here.  - Keys!
- 给你 - 钥匙!
What's happening? Where are you taking me?
发生什么事儿了? 你要把我带到哪儿去?
Put your seatbelt on.
系上安全带
Shit!
该死!
- What's your name?  - Scott.
- 你叫什么名字?  - Scott
- I'm Mallory.  - Hi.
- 我叫Mallory  - 嗨
You're gonna fix my arm while we drive. Okay, Scott?
我来开车 你帮我包扎伤口 行吗 Scott?
Yeah.
好
Okay. Here. Ready?
好了 是这儿 准备好了吗?
- Okay.  - Now take two of the dry packets,
- 好了  - 拿两个止血包
put them on the one you already have in place.
放在这块上面
- Yeah?  - Now take the tape,
- 然后呢?  - 现在拿胶带
wrap it around the gauze so it stays on my arm.
把纱布固定在我胳膊上
- Tight.  - Yeah.
- 包紧点  - 嗯
- Sorry.  - Couple times around.
- 抱歉  - 绕几圈
- Watch your arm.  - Yeah.
- 当心你的胳膊  - 好
Okay, now tape... Use the scissors to cut it.
好了 现在胶带... 用剪刀剪断
- Okay.  - Okay.
- 好的  - 好了
That should be good for now.
暂时应该没事了
Jesus Christ.
天呐
- I'm hyperventilating.  - Scott.
- 我都喘不过气来了  - Scott
Thank you.
谢谢
Yeah, sure.
嗯 不客气
So, who...
那 他...
Who was that guy?
那个家伙是谁?
- I mean, honestly.  - Aaron?
- 我是说 实实在在的  - Aaron吗?
Someone I worked with.
我以前的一个同事
- Was he your... you know.  - No.
- 他以前是你的... 你知道的  - 不是
No.
不是
Where did you work with him?
你跟他在哪里工作过啊?
Barcelona.
巴塞罗那
I...
我...
I don't mean to, you know, get personal.
我没有打探你个人隐私的意思
- Are you in the drug business?  - No.
- 你在做毒品生意吗?  - 不是
Are you with the government?
你在帮政府部门做事吗?
They contracted a company I work for.
政府部门跟我所在的公司有合约
Private company.
私人公司
Wow. That's actually real?
哇哦 那是真的吗?
- Yeah.  - That makes sense.
- 是的  - 难怪呢
So what do you do? What's your job?
那你到底是干什么的? 你的工作是什么?
华盛顿特区
Barcelona. Separatists?
巴塞罗那 是分离分子?
No, no. It's clean.
不 不是 就是个单纯的绑架
Negotiations broke down, just need somebody to go and get the guy.
谈判破裂了 需要派人过去救出这个人
Okay, whatever.
好吧 管他呢
巴塞罗那
In four points,
四个条件
a better immunity language, more access to intelligence,
更多的豁免权 更多的情报
this fee structure is unacceptable.
这点费用是不够的
Intelligence?
情报?
Yeah, I need parity with Rodrigo here and all his people.
是的 我得跟Rodrigo和他的手下分享情报
You're with state, right?
你是政府的人 对吗?
Yes.
是的
You like it?
你喜欢那里吗?
I like the idea of me doing my job
我喜欢自己从事的工作
more than the idea of someone else doing my job.
总比别人做我的工作强
All right, now the immunity language is as good as we can do.
好 豁免条件我们可以满足
Fee structure... A number?
费用嘛... 说个数字?
Yeah, we need to adjust the overall payment
是的 得调高一下预算总额
in order that we can address things like hazard bumps.
以防紧急情况发生
I'll make a list. But also how the installments are spaced.
我会列一个单子 但也包括每一部分的具体划分
Fewer steps.
较少的步骤
Hi.
嗨
Hey.
嘿
What, am I first?
我是第一个到的吗?
Yeah, Victor will be here at 4:30, and Jamie's running late.
是的 Victor四点半到 而Jamie要迟到一会儿
There's always a cash flow problem.
现金流水总有问题
This is a short timetable, Kenneth. Should I be nervous?
时间不多了 Kenneth 你们能让我放心吗?
If it will make you feel better,
如果你想放心的话
you can get the people that did the Mexico job, Alex.
你可以去找那些在墨西哥执行过任务的人 Alex
Look, I know it's more efficient if we wait for everybody to get here,
听着 我知道人到齐了会更有效率
but you want to start going through this? I've got some ideas.
但你想现在就开始做的话? 我有些想法
You're right. It's more efficient if we wait for everyone to get here.
你说得对 人到齐了才会更有效率
This should be fun.
这应该挺有意思的
- Your kit's under your bed.  - Yours check out?
- 你的装备放在你床下了  - 你检查过了?
- Good to go.  - I'll check later then, thank you.
- 没问题  - 我待会去看看 谢谢
There's no smoking in here.
这里禁止吸烟
Okay.
好吧
It's a phone.
这是手机
Tell me about Kenneth.
跟我谈谈Kenneth的情况吧
What about him?
他哪方面?
How long have you worked together?
你们在一起工作多长时间了?
Three years.
三年
Not so long.
不太长
It is in this business.
在这行中是不太长
You said four points.
你说了四个条件
You have Mallory Kane as an essential element.
你说Mallory Kane必须参加
Is that a problem?
有什么问题吗?
Not a good precedent for me, for my business.
这对我的生意来说 不是个好先例
Well, it doesn't work for us if she's not involved.
呃 如果她不参加的话 我们就没法做下去了
She's not available.
她没空
You mind if I call and check on that?
你介意我打电话核实一下吗?
I didn't realize your interest extended to personnel.
我没想到你会关心我们的人员组成
No, no. No, when somebody's good, it comes to my attention.
不 不 不是 当某人特别优秀的时候 我就会注意到的
It's come to my attention you're spreading yourself a little thin.
我还注意到你最近管的有点宽啊
Kenneth, I don't want your B-team. She's value-added.
Kenneth 我不想要你的二流团队 她是个增值品
Only reason we came to you.
这也是我们找你来做这事的唯一原因
All right, I'll free her up.
好的 我会调她过来
And I'll forego the hazard bumps if you remove the essential element clause.
我会放弃额外的费用 如果你不用她的话
- That important, huh?  - Do you want her in Barcelona or not?
- 她这么重要吗 哈?  - 你要不要她去巴塞罗那?
人质
江在巴塞罗那失踪
头号坏人
时间窗口: 3.5-4分钟
Explain it to me then. So I can understand it.
谁给我解释一下啊 这样我才能理解啊
How are we not light?
我们人手怎么就不少了?
So we have a man in the car, we got a man at the door.
我们车内留一个人 门口一个人
Leaves you two to breach with.
只剩下你们两人行动了
You're going hot on a hostage rescue.
你们可是要去解救人质啊
There's two rooms inside.
里面有两个房间
So, the way I read it,
因此 在我看来
you're either two men short in one room, or you're one man short in each room.
如果你们两人搭档只能进一个房间 如果你们各自进一个房间 又没有搭档
Anyone else think we're light?
还有人觉得我们人手不够吗?
Us?
我们?
No way.
不觉得
Good to go.
没问题
那就没问题吧
You tracking me with the names?
你记得我说的名字吗?
Repeat them.
重复一遍
Mallory. Kenneth. Aaron.
Mallory Kenneth Aaron啊
Jamie. Victor. Rodrigo.
Jamie Victor Rodrigo啊
Barcelona.
巴塞罗那
Hostage name.
人质名字
- Yang.  - Jiang.
- 杨  - 江
Shit. Jiang. Jiang.
该死 江 江
Don't speak. Walk in front of me.
别说话 走在我前面
If I touch you, drop to your knees. Do you understand?
如果我碰你的话 你就趴跪下 明白了吗?
Done.
搞定了
They all gone?
他们都走了?
Yeah.
是的
When that guy took off, why'd you chase him?
那个人逃跑的时候 你为什么要去追?
We already had Jiang in the backseat.
我们已经救出江了
I don't like loose ends.
我不想留下后患
Is this your idea of relaxing?
这是你放松的方式?
Wine and gun maintenance?
喝酒和保养枪支?
There's another glass in the kitchen.
厨房里还有酒杯
You gonna leave your name and number afterwards?
你待会留下你的名字和电话号码吧?
Why? You want it?
为什么? 你想要吗?
You're gonna leave Kenneth?
你要离开Kenneth吗?
I left Kenneth six months ago.
我六个月前就跟Kenneth分手了
I meant the company.
我是指公司
You're gonna leave the company?
你要离开公司吗?
Company, I left an hour ago.
公司 我一个小时前就离开了
How come?
为什么?
'Cause I'm not going down with the ship.
因为我不想跟船一起沉下去
Are you?
你想吗?
If he's paying, yeah, I'm staying.
如果他付钱的话 我就会留下
If you stay...
如果你也留下...
I don't know, maybe...
我不太清楚 或许...
圣地亚哥
沙漠中的袭击
Mallory 你又过生日了 爱你的父亲
Hi.
嗨
What are you doing here?
你在这里干什么?
Gate key still worked.
门钥匙还能用
I didn't change everyone's locks, just mine.
我没换别人的锁 只换了我的
Hey, I came by, 'cause you weren't picking up.
嘿 我过来是因为你老不接我电话
- I just landed.  - Yeah, two hours ago.
- 我刚下飞机  - 是啊 两个小时了
I've been away for nine weeks. That was my third job in a row.
我都离开九个星期了 连着做了三个任务
Give me a break.
让我休息一下吧
You wouldn't know what to do with a break.
你根本不知道该怎么休息
You think you know me?
你觉得你了解我吗?
I know you.
我确实了解
I bet he's just like his books.
我猜他一定人如其书
- What?  - Your father.
- 谁?  - 你的父亲
I bet he's just like the characters in his books.
他肯定跟书里的角色一样
How would you know?
你怎么知道?
You've never read one of his books and you've never met him.
你从没读过他的书 你也从没见过他
I'm just going off his photograph.
我看过他的相片
What do you want?
你想干什么?
The usual. I have an assignment.
和往常一样 我有份合同
Well, your timing sucks. I haven't even unpacked yet.
呃 时间很不巧 我还没放好行李呢
This'll take no time at all. It's like a paid holiday.
这个不会花很多时间的 就像次带薪休假
This will take no time at all starting when?
这个假期什么时候开始呢?
Well, tonight.
好吧 今晚
I mean, you would have to leave tonight.
我是说 你今晚就得出发
Well, if it is a paid holiday, then it doesn't have to be me.
如果这是次带薪休假任务 那就没必要派我去
I'm overqualified.
杀鸡焉用牛刀啊
The client has asked for you.
客户指定要求你去
Mallory, it's Ml6. It's a new in for me. I can expand.
Mallory 这次可是M16 他们是第一次来找公司 这是我扩展业务的机会
Yeah, sounds great. For you.
是的 对你来说 听起来不错
Let me turn the volume up a little here.
你我再说明白一点
You probably heard me mention the name Paul.
你可能听我提及过Paul吧
Paul. Never, not once.
Paul 从来没有
Well, Paul, he's one of us, but he's freelance.
呃 Paul 他是我们的一员 但他是自由职业者
Actually, I was hoping you might convince him to come aboard,
事实上 我也希望你能劝他回公司干
but that's secondary.
但那是次要的
Paul has managed to get close to a curious character named Studer,
Paul认识了一个叫Studer的怪咖
and our client wants to take advantage of this.
我们的客户想利用这点
Studer is a French national residing in Ireland.
Studer是定居在爱尔兰的法国公民
It's tricky, they want a light footprint.
关系很微妙 他们希望能不留痕迹
- Well, you've got Paul.  - I've got Paul, but Paul...
- 你不是有Paul嘛  - 我是有Paul 但他...
Paul has presented himself as one half of a power couple.
Paul想和你一起乔装成一对大腕夫妇
This is your pitch?
这就是你的目的?
You want me to be eye candy?
你想让我当个花瓶?
Ml6 wants me to be eye candy?
M16想让我当个花瓶?
Mallory, you are the eye.
Mallory 你是核心
I don't even know how to play that.
我不知道怎么去扮演那个角色
I don't wear the dress.
我都不穿连衣裙
- Make Paul wear the dress.  - Well, I'll ask.
- 让Paul穿吧  - 好的 我会问问他的
Look, do this and then we'll go away afterwards. We'll go to Majorca.
听着 干完这票 我们就离开 我们去Majorca
- Majorca?  - Not like before, as friends.
- Majorca?  - 跟以前不一样 只是作为普通朋友
You can take a break.
你可以休个假
It's literally two days.
只需要两天
Paul. That's Paul.
Paul 这就是Paul
You guys would be like the perfect couple.
你们一定会像是一对甜蜜的情侣的
So he'll know you.
这样他就会知道你是谁了
I need this to happen.
我得做好这次任务
- Hi.  - Hi.
- 嗨  - 嗨
都柏林
My better half. You look great.
我的另一半 你看起来真美
Mind if I freshen up first?
介意我先去冲凉吗?
Presumably, you'll need more time.
貌似 你应该需要更长时间
Go ahead.
去吧
All yours.
你可以洗了
Wow. You look fantastic.
哇哦 你看起来美极了
Can you zip me?
你能帮我拉上拉链吗?
Of course.
当然
- I'm leaving my gun.  - Me, too.
- 我不带枪  - 我也是
Shall we?
走吧?
Russborough. Remember Russborough.
Russborough 要记住Russborough
Russborough.
好的 Russborough
Who's Russborough?
谁是Russborough?
Not a who. A what. A place.
不是人名 是个地名
It's where we were supposed to meet Studer.
那里我们应该能遇到Studer
Not your natural habitat, is it?
这不是常来的地方 对吧?
Wrong side of the tracks.
选错了边
Kept getting into fights.
麻烦不断
Bleak future.
前途无望
Kenneth knows how to put trouble to good use.
Kenneth知道怎么化干戈为玉帛的
I'm empty.
我喝完了
- You have family?  - Both parents, still going strong.
- 你成家了吗?  - 双方父母都在健在 身体硬朗
Teachers.
是做老师的
Two brothers and a rather adorable niece.
两个兄弟和一个可爱的侄女
Whiskey.
来杯威士忌
- They know what you do?  - No.
- 他们知道你做什么的嘛?  - 不知道
I can never lie to my dad.
我从来不对我父亲说谎
Then he must worry about you.
那他肯定担心死你了
I tell him not to.
我跟他说了没有必要
Still keeping tabs?
他还在管着你吗?
I hate babysitting jobs.
我最讨厌被人管着了
That guy just recognized me.
那个人刚刚认出我了
- Who?  - Gray shirt, gray tie, goatee.
- 谁?  - 那个穿灰衬衫 灰领带 山羊胡子的人
- You sure?  - Yeah.
- 你确定嘛?  - 确定
Why would he know you?
为什么他认识你?
'Cause the last time I saw him, I was in Baghdad in my hotel room.
因为上次遇到他的时候 我是在巴格达酒店的房间里
All right. Here comes our friend.
好吧 那我们去会一下老朋友
Well, it's obvious you're newlyweds.
你们很明显是新婚夫妻嘛
Still talking to each other instead of the other guests.
一直互相间甜蜜 都没怎么和其他客人聊天啊
- I'm sorry. Are we being rude?  - No, no.
- 不好意思 我们失礼了?  - 没有 没有
- Katie, Eric Studer.  - Hi.
- 这位是Katie 这位是Eric Studer  - 你好
Listen, I had some brainwave. What are you two doing afterwards?
话说 我刚刚突发奇想 之后你们有什么打算吗?
Well, I don't know. You're jet-lagged, right?
我不清楚 你还在倒时差 不是吗?
No, I'm sorry. I mean tomorrow, this week.
对不起 我是指明天 或者这周
No particular plans.
没计划呢
- We were going back to London.  - London?
- 我们本打算回伦敦去的  - 回伦敦?
I may have better than this.
我或许有更好的去处
We're going to Saint Moritz.
我们打算去Saint Moritz
- We?  - Yeah, some friends.
- 我们?  - 是的 还有些朋友一起去
It'll be fun. We'll fly in, put you up at Suvretta.
肯定很有意思的 我们飞过去 你们就在Suvretta下
- Well...  - Do you ski?
- 这样啊...  - 你会滑雪吗?
- Snowboard.  - These are the Alps, they're pretty steep.
- 会滑雪板  - 那里算阿尔卑斯山的 坡度还满陡的
Like the prices. We'll discuss it.
那价格的话 我们到时候商量一下
No, no, no discussion. We go.
不用 不用商量 我们一起去吧
I'll send the itinerary to your hotel.
我会把行程表送到你们的旅馆
Wheels up at 11 :00.
11点整我们出发
Okay? Okay?
好吗? 好吗?
You locate goatee. I'll take Studer.
你去找那山羊胡 我去搞定Studer
Myself and a few friends are heading to a nice little village.
我和一群朋友要去个漂亮的小镇
Maybe you could come and join us.
你们也许能跟我们一起去
- Sounds good.  - Yeah.
- 听起来不错啊  - 是啊
Bet you look good in white. Fluffy, little bunny.
我打赌白色会把你衬的很好看 加点绒毛 小绒毛的那种
全球定位跟踪器F1
I should think Sunday.
我觉得是星期天吧
Sunday?
星期天?
Maybe Saturday, if we're lucky.
如果运气好的话 可能是星期六
Then let's be lucky.
那就运气好一点吧
- Mrs. Hillier.  - Hi Katie.
- Hillier夫人  - 嗨 Katie
Katie. You haven't promised to come skiing.
Katie 你还没答应来滑雪呢
I can't even find my way around here.
我在这里都快迷路了
Richard is in the other room. I just left him.
Richard在另外一间屋子 我刚刚从那里过来
Well, actually, I was looking for the...
实际上 我是在找...
Oh, they're in the back of the library.
哦 他们在图书室后面
So much wine.
喝太多酒了
- So much to look at.  - Yeah.
- 摆设真是琳琅满目啊  - 是啊
You've only seen the inside. I should show you the maze.
但你只看了屋子里的 我应该带你去看看屋外的迷宫
Isn't it a little dark out there?
外面天不是应该有点黑了吗?
Perfect time.
时间刚好
I get claustrophobic, even in the daytime.
我有幽闭恐怖症 就算白天也会发作的
No, the whole point is to relax and lose yourself.
不会的 重点就是要放松 迷失自己
I'll take a rain check.
下次吧
This is Ireland. Won't be long.
这里可是爱尔兰 花不了太长时间的
And to find your way back, retrace your steps.
如果要回来的话 原路返回就行
Fuck.
擦
Hi.
嗨
- Where are you?  - In the bathroom.
- 你在哪里?  - 在卫生间
I'm not used to drinking so much.
我喝太多了
My friend from Baghdad has a date. Well, a couple, actually.
我那巴格达的朋友有女伴 好几个女伴
I think it's the paid-for kind.
肯定是花钱找来的
Where are you?
你在哪里?
In the main room.
我在主客厅
I spoke to Studer briefly and made our apologies,
我跟Studer谈了一会 并表达了我们的歉意
told him we'd discuss Saint Moritz in the morning.
跟他说了 我们明早再讨论去圣莫里茨的事情
I think we should get back to the hotel and talk to Kenneth, don't you?
我觉得我们应该回旅馆 跟Kenneth聊聊 你觉得呢?
Thank you.
谢谢
Mallory, you're in way over your head.
Mallory 你已经无法理智了
Think this through.
好好想想
You've been out of control since you've arrived.
你到了这里 就已经失控了
You need to call Kenneth.
你应该打个电话给Kenneth
你有1个未接电话 2段电话录音
Excuse me. I should take this.
不好意思 我要接个电话
Pauly?
Pauly吗?
So, is the divorce final?
婚最后离成了吗?
Paul, are you there?
Paul, 你还在吗?
Mallory.
是Mallory吧
新墨西哥州
- Hello.  - Dad, it's Mal.
- 喂  - 爸爸 我是Mal
Things are kind of screwed up here and I need to come home.
这里事情出了点问题 我需要回家一趟
It may take me a couple of days, depending on what happens.
可能要在呆上一段时间 具体要看发生了什么事
Don't worry about me, you just get here as quick as you can.
不用担心我 你尽快回来就行了
I'll try.
我尽量吧
Keep your eyes open.
自己留个心眼
I haven't shut my eyes since you were born.
你生下来以后 我浑身都是心眼
Just be careful.
自己当心一点
And watch your six.
严防暗箭啊
I will.
我知道了
I'll see you at the house.
到时候家里见吧
未知来电
- Can I get this cell phone?  - It's 42.50.
- 这个手机多少钱?  - 42.5欧元
There you go.
钱给你
Come on, let's go, let's go. Get over there. Let's go. Come on.
快走 快走 走这边 快走
Rodrigo. Hi, it's Mallory Kane.
Rodrigo 嗨 我是Mallory Kane
- Mallory Kane.  - I hope it's not too late.
- Mallory Kane  - 希望不算太迟
I just landed in New York. Do you have a minute?
我刚刚飞到纽约 你有空吗?
I just felt like I had to call. I was going over my report,
我只是觉得应该打个电话 我刚刚还在看我的报告
and I realized I never thanked you for all your help.
才发现你帮了我这么多 我都没回谢你
It's really not necessary. It's not even customary.
这真的不必要 你也没这种习惯的吧
Well, it should be.
这应该要有的
But I just wanted to verify one thing with you before I actually file my report.
我只是想在你归档我报告之前 核对一件事情
Was it you or Kenneth who sold the Barcelona job to Studer?
是你还是Kenneth把巴塞罗那这情报卖给Studer的?
Rodrigo.
Rodrigo好啊
What are you working so late for? It's what, past 8: 00, your time?
你这么晚在做什么呢? 你那边差不多过了8点了吧
Yeah. Listen, Mallory Kane just called me.
是啊 听着 Mallory Kane刚刚打个电话给我
I thought you should know.
我和你说一声
- Wait, she called you at home?  - Yes.
- 等一下 她打到你家里的?  - 是的
Was that a nice conversation?
你们聊得还愉快吗?
Yeah, yeah, very nice. Brief, but very nice. Yeah.
愉快 很是愉快 很简短 但聊得很开心
She thanked me for my assistance.
她是来感谢之前我的帮助的
She still in Dublin?
她还在都柏林吗?
She said she just landed in New York.
她说她刚刚飞到纽约
Good.
好的
Good. Well, why don't you stay off your house line,
好的 家里的电话别再接了
and I wouldn't go outside till I call you back.
在我打电话给你之前 你和你家人最好
Or your family.
别出门
- I see. Thank you.  - All right.
- 我知道了 谢谢  - 好的
Rodrigo, you take care, all right?
Rodrigo 自己小心点 好吗?
Yeah, sure. Bye.
好的 再见
Tyler, the activity log for the number that I just sent you,
Tyler 我刚刚发给你的行动日志
I want you to connect me to the last incoming call.
我需要你帮我接通最后那个来电
Who is this?
谁打来的?
Mallory, hi. My name is Alex Coblenz.
Mallory 嗨 我叫Alex Coblenz
I was with Kenneth and Rodrigo when the Barcelona deal went down.
巴塞罗那任务失败的时候 我和Kenneth Rodrigo在一起
Who else besides you knows about this?
除了你 还有谁知道这事情的?
No, only the people that need to know in order to fix it.
没了 就只有那些后续任务的保密人员
The people who thought up Barcelona.
那些发出巴塞罗那任务的人
Mallory, we did not think up Barcelona.
Mallory 巴塞罗那任务不是我们发出的
No, you just helped.
好吧 你们只是推了把手
- Can you bring me in?  - We can, yes,
- 你能渗透我进去吗?  - 可以的 我们能做到
but I'd like you to keep doing what you're doing.
但我想要你继续做你现在做的事情
We want you to bust Kenneth's budget, you know, see how he reacts.
我们想要你搅乱Kenneth的计划 看看他作何反应
Everyone he reaches out to, you know, it's like another layer.
他派出的每个人 都处于不同层面上
What do you think he's into?
我觉得他的目的是什么?
Well, whatever it is, Kenneth is not at the top.
不管是什么 Kenneth背后还是有人的
It's just not possible. We like Studer. We think there's something there.
完全就不可能 我们趋向Studer 觉得那里有会有些线索
You gotta get me off the watch list.
那你必须取消对我的通缉啊
Mallory, I... I cannot do that.
Mallory 这点我... 我做不到
You know, while Kenneth's watching, he'll know we spoke.
你懂的 到处都是Kenneth的眼线 我们的事会败露的
I promise I'll do everything I can to convince him to meet you.
我保证我尽我所能说服他去见你
Then you can find out what we both want to know,
这样你就能找出我们双方都想知道的消息了
which is why this is happening.
这也是这通电话的目的
I got a fake ID in London, came in through Canada,
我在伦敦弄了张假证件 飞到了加拿大
and crossed the border.
穿过了国境线
Coblenz helped me set up a meeting with Kenneth, but Aaron showed up instead.
Coblenz帮我安排了和Kenneth的见面 但半路杀出个Aaron
And then I met you.
然后我就遇到你了
There's some water in my backpack.
我背包里还有些水
Have some.
喝点吧
Don't mind if I do. Thank you.
你不介意我直接喝吧 谢谢
- You want some?  - Yeah, please.
- 你要喝点吗?  - 好的 谢谢
- Help me.  - Yeah, sorry.
- 帮我一把  - 好的 不好意思
- Good?  - Yeah. Thanks.
- 够了吗?  - 够了 谢谢
What's going on here?
那边什么情况?
Random road check?
普通道路检查吧?
All right. Hold on.
好吧 坐稳了
Yep.
好吧
Jesus!
老天啊!
Jeez!
天啊!
I just got this car, like, a week ago.
这车可是我刚买的啊 才买了一个星期啊
Yeah, well...
是吗 好吧...
Whoops, more LEOs.
啊哦 LEO
What's a LEO?
LEO是什么?
Law enforcement officers.
执法人员
Shit!
见鬼!
Shit! Watch the car!
见鬼! 当心那车!
That was nice. That was nice. That was really bad.
躲的好 躲的好 真是千钧一发啊
I thought that was gonna be really bad for a second.
我还以为我们完蛋了呢
I thought I was gonna have a heart attack. Oh, my God.
我还以为我心要跳出来了 老天爷啊
Jesus Christ! You are a great driver!
老天爷啊! 你开车可真有一手啊!
- Are you okay?  - Yeah, are you?
- 你没事吧?  - 没事 你呢?
Yeah. Oh, my God! There's a deer in the car.
没事 我的天啊 有头鹿在车里面
- Jesus...  - Yeah, I know.
- 天啊...  - 我注意到了
- Should we run?  - No. Don't.
- 我们应该逃跑吗?  - 不用 不用了
We've done enough.
我们已经尽力了
Show me your hands.
把手举起来
- Freeze! Don't move!  - You, behind the car, step forward!
- 站住! 别动!  - 在车后面的那个 走到车前面来!
Hands in the air! Turn around!
把手举起来! 转过身去!
Turn around, punk!
转过身去 混蛋!
Unit three.
呼叫三组
三组收到
Proceed with suspects to 2345 Clearview.
将嫌犯带至Clearview2345号
Repeat, 2345 Clearview, and hold.
重复 带至Clearview2345号 并等待
Federal agents en route.
联邦探员正在赶来
Unit three, copy.
三组 收到
You must have stepped in something.
你一定撞上什么大案子了
Yeah.
是啊
Excuse me, Deputy Cross?
打扰一下 Cross副警长?
Deputy Cross? Hi.
Cross副警长? 嗨
You were in the Corps, right? I was a devil dog.
你参过军 对吧? 我也曾是海军陆战队队员
Listen, this might sound a little funny.
听着 这可能听上去有点可笑
I'm a private contractor on a 10-24 operation,
我是执行任务的私人探员
and these guys you're about to meet are not federal agents.
你们待会见的那些人不是什么联邦探员
I mean, follow your protocol and all,
我是说 你们照着规定办事
but you should really keep your distance.
但记得保持距离
Use your radio and your loudspeakers in order to confirm who these guys aren't.
利用电台和扩音器来确定那群人的真假
Really, I'm not joking.
说真的 我不是开玩笑
You can look me up, a New Mexico license for Mallory Kane.
你能搜我的身 上面有叫Mallory Kane的新墨西哥执照
I'll confirm the number.
我能确认那些号码
You need to sit back.
你给我乖乖坐在后排
Look, an innocent civilian will be killed if you do not listen to me.
听着 你们不听我劝的话 可是要死无辜的人的
Hey, Wonder Woman, you sold your piece. Now sit back and shut up.
嘿 神奇女侠 故事讲完了吗 现在闭上嘴坐回去
- Jesus, are you...  - Get down!
- 天啊 你是...  - 趴下!
Just keep your head down a few more minutes and you're out of this.
就趴下一会儿 然后你就没事了
Great, great. How are you gonna get out of this, may I ask?
好吧 好吧 那你怎么办 能告诉我吗?
I'll just dump the car. I'll find another ride. I'll catch a bus.
我会把车给丢了 再找一辆车 或者坐公交车
Great, good luck with that.
好极了 祝你好运啊
I can't wait till Coblenz hears about this.
我不能等到Coblenz了解情况了(TBD)
- What is that?  - Listen, when we split,
- 什么情况?  - 听着 等我们分开之后
I'm gonna give you a number to call.
我会给你一个电话号码 让你去打
I was supposed to be sleeping in late today,
早知道今天我就起晚点了
not getting carjacked.
就不会遇到打劫的了
Scott, you still with me?
Scott 你听见我说的了吗?
- Yeah, yeah. Yeah, a number.  - Just tell them everything.
- 听到了 听到了 电话号码  - 跟他们讲发生的一切
Tell the police, too, tell them everything I've told you, okay?
告诉他们警察的事 告诉他们我跟你说的一切 记住了吗?
- Yeah, okay.  - You did great.
- 记住了 好的  - 之前你做的很好
- You're gonna be fine.  - Yeah. Okay.
- 你肯定会没事的  - 好的 好的吧
This is the trouble, with the private sector, Kenneth.
这就是问题所在 那些私营部门 Kenneth
You got that macho takedown, but where's the due diligence?
你的条件我们都答应了 但你应有的努力呢?
Where's the follow-through?
我想要的结果呢?
Now, we got ourselves a real twizzler here.
如今 我们进退两难
And for eight figures, I don't accept excuses,
为了那八位数的投入 我不接受任何借口
explanations or rationales.
解释或者理由
Now I don't even know why the hell you're standing here.
我都不知道你为什么还再站在这里
You should be in her father's living room, explaining to him,
你应该在她爸客厅里 跟他解释清楚
telling him that his daughter is a fugitive with ties to terrorists.
告诉他 他的女儿是个和恐怖分子有联系的逃犯
That she killed a man in cold blood in Dublin and killed four cops.
她在柏林冷血的杀了一个男人和四个警察
You tell him.
你告诉他
Show him.
让他瞧瞧
He'll come at you like he's government,make me seem like a monster.
他会以政府的名义来找你 把我说成女魔头
Play like you're shocked.
你要装的很震惊
The guy with the broken arm, Aaron,
手臂受伤的男人 是Aaron
get in his head.
打扰他的思路
Keep bringing up Barcelona.
不断的提到巴塞罗那
Get him arguing with Kenneth.
让他和Kenneth吵起来
Kenneth.
Kenneth
My fault. I should've seen that one coming.
我的错 我早就该预料到的
You did.
像你一样
Hold on a sec, Mal.Let's analyze your options.
等一下 Mal 我们考虑一下你现有的选择
We could leave right now, disappear.
我们可以立刻离开 人间蒸发
We could be in Buenos Aires this time tomorrow.
明天的这个时候 我们可能已经到了布宜诺斯艾利斯(阿根廷首都)
I'm not gonna run anymore.
我再也不想逃跑了
Mr. Kane, these were taken by the police. They're pretty graphic.
Kane先生 这些是警方拍的 非常明显
Her prints are all over the room.
房间到处是她的指纹
The security video shows them coming in together and her leaving alone.
保安监控录像显示他们一起进去 然后她独自离开
The guest downstairs complained about the noise.
楼下的客人抱怨太吵
Paul fought back,
Paul当时在反抗
but she obviously had the element of surprise in her favor.
但是很明显 她的出其不意使她占据上风
She choked him out and she shot him in the head.
她将他掐晕 并在他的头上补了一枪
Add that to the four police,and that is five dead in three days.
外加上四名警察 三天内五人死于其手
- Where was she last seen?  - Upstate New York, 36 hours ago.
- 她最后一次出现在哪?  - 纽约州北部 36小时以前
- Was she alone?  - No, she was with a boy, 19.
- 她一个人吗?  - 不 她和一个19岁的男孩
She grabbed him at gunpoint.Used him as a ride and a shield,
她挟持了他 逼他开车 并当作人质
so we can add aggravated kidnapping to the murder charges.
所以我们可以在控告她谋杀时添上一项恶性绑架的罪名
No, I'm sorry.
不 抱歉
This doesn't sound like my daughter.
听上去不像我女儿
She ever mention the name Kenneth?
她从来没有提过Kenneth吗?
No.
没有
Really?
真的?
He runs the company she worked for.
他是她的老板
They were in a relationship for over a year, and yet she never mentioned him to you?
他们曾经恋爱过一年多 但她从没向您提起过他?
What do you know about her?
你了解她什么?
Really, at the end of the day?
事实上 到头来你了解她吗？
I raised her.
我一手把她拉扯大
And denial is a very effective parenting tool.
否认也是一种有效的养育方式
She was a Marine. She does something,there must be a reason for it.
她曾经是名海军陆战队士兵 她的所作所为 一定事出有因
Mr. Kane, she is no longer a Marine.She is a murderer.
Kane先生 她不再是士兵了 她是杀人凶手
She is a public threat.She's on a killing spree.
她是公众威胁 她现在杀戮成性
Now, you are the only person that she can trust.
现在 你是她唯一能信任的人
You're gonna help bring her in before she kills again.
在她再次杀戮前 你应该协助我们逮捕她
Without you, she won't survive this.
不然的话 她无法幸免
I heard from her.
她联系过我
Ten days ago.
十天以前
She texted me,said she was going to Barcelona.
她给我发短信 告诉我她将要去巴塞罗那
What did she say exactly?
她具体怎么说的?
"Going to Barcelona. Call you after."
"将去巴塞罗那 晚点给您电话"
Six words, that's it?
六个字 就这样?
Well, it was enough for me.
是的 这样我已经很满足了
And she didn't mention Dublin? She didn't say anything about this?
她没有提过都柏林(爱尔兰共和国首都)? 一点也没提到吗?
No.
没有
Who was he?
死者是什么人?
He was an agent with British Intelligence.
他曾是英国情报机关的一名特工
Now, whether this was a murder-for-hire or a crime of passion, we don't know.
目前 我们还不清楚这起案件是雇佣谋杀还是情杀
Well, she would never kill someone for money.
喂 她不可能为了钱杀人
There must be an explanation.
一定另有内情
Didn't this all start after Barcelona?
这些事不都是源于巴塞罗那之后吗?
Maybe that has something to do with why she's a fugitive.
她为何逃亡也许和那个有关
Something must have happened there.
那里一定发生了什么
- Aaron. - I'm on it.
- Aaron  - 交给我
It's overseas. Prepaid phone.Yeah, that's gotta be her.
国外的 预付电话 对 肯定是她
Wait for the track.
等待追踪
Go.
接吧
Talk to her.
和她说话
Mallory.
Mallory
Dad, don't say anything.Give Kenneth the phone.
爸 不要说什么 把电话给Kenneth
Just be careful.
小心一点
Mallory, I hope you've decided to turn yourself in.
Mallory 我希望你已经决定自首
You can tell me right now why you sold me out
你现在可以告诉我 为什么出卖我
and what you're into with Studer,
以及 你和Studer想要干什么
or you can tell me in ten minutes,
给你十分钟
when I have my hands around your throat.
否则我会亲手掐死你
You need to think for a minute, Mallory.
你需要冷静一下 Mallory
You need to stop pretending
别装模作样了
you can achieve a desirable outcome in this situation,
别以为在这种情况下你还能力挽狂澜
and turn yourself in.
还是自首吧
Do it for the sake of your father.
为了你的父亲
Surrender now if you wanna live.
如果想要保命你就投降吧
I'm sorry, Mallory, that's not possible.
抱歉 Mallory 这不可能
All right, Kenneth. We'll do it your way.
好吧 Kenneth 我们按你的方法来
She's...
她在...
She's here.
她在这
Here? Where?
这儿?哪儿?
In the house. Track says she's in the house. Go, now. You sit down.
就在房子里 追踪器显示她就在房子里 快去  你坐好
You knew about this? You knew she was here?
你早知道是吧? 你知道她在这?
No. I told you, I haven't heard from her since she texted me.
不 我告诉过你 收到短信后她就没联系过我了
Kenny.
Kenny
Do we need to have a conversation about Barcelona?
我们是不是该谈谈关于巴塞罗那的事？
Aaron, you were in Barcelona. You know what happened.
Aaron 你当时在巴塞罗那 你知道发生了什么
We rescued a man.
我们救了一个男人
- Did we?  - Aaron, you need to focus right now.
- 真的吗?  - Aaron 你现在需要立刻集中精力
You were in Barcelona?
你当时也在巴塞罗那吗？
I'm confused. She works for a private company.
我很疑惑 她为一家私营公司工作
Breaker box. Get on it. Lock the doors.
电源总闸 去检查一下 把门都锁上
- What if she's inside? - Then we'll pressure-cook her.
- 如果她在里面怎么办？  - 那我们就逼她出来
We'll find her.
会找到她的
I don't mean to tell you your job,
我并不是有意提醒你
but isn't there someone you should be calling, Agent Milgrom?
但是你是不是应该给谁打个电话 Milgrom探员?
Other officers of the law, to bring help?
其它的警官 请他们来帮忙？
We can handle this.
我们能处理
- Go. - I got this. Watch him.
- 上  -我来 你看着他
- Did you hear that?- Yeah.
- 你听到了吗？  - 嗯
Get on it.
继续找
Tom's down. IED in the breaker box.
Tom挂了 电源总闸里放了IED(临时炸弹装置)
- We need to get to the car. - I'm not sure if that'll help.
- 我们去车里  - 我觉得这样没用
But she can't outrun a car.
她不可能跑的比车快
She can if it's not running.
如果车抛锚了她就可以
Well, then let's find out.
那就快把她找出来
Be my guest. Go ahead.
请自便 去吧
You should see this.
你应该看看这个
Who did that? Her?
谁发给你的? 她吗?
- Yeah, probably. That's why we're here.  - Doesn't make any sense, man.
- 可能是 这就是我们在这的原因  - 这到底是什么意思
- Aaron, let's not discuss this right now.  - No. We're gonna talk about it.
- Aaron 我们现在别讨论这个  - 不 我们现在就要谈谈
- Calm down.  - Don't tell me to calm down.
- 冷静  - 不要叫我冷静
- What did you do?  - I did what I was contracted to do.
- 你做了什么?  - 我都是按合同执行的
We were contracted to rescue somebody.
我们的合同是救人
It seems to me, you auctioned him off and tried to burn her.
在我看来 你处理掉他 然后嫁祸给她
- That's not what happened. - Really?
- 不是这样的  -真的吗?
- No, I can explain.  - Then explain it,
- 是的 我可以解释  - 那解释吧
and try really hard.
尽力解释
Don't give me a reason.
不要逼我
No, just go help her!
不 快去帮她
- Kenneth!  - He's gone.
- Kenneth!  - 他逃走了
You better run.
你最好快跑
I'm so stupid.
我太蠢了
Can't believe I met you a week ago.
我简直不敢相信一星期前我遇到你
Eight, eight days.
八天 是八天
We were in Barcelona eight days ago?
八天前我们在巴塞罗那吗?
I'm trying to focus on my breathing.
我正试着把注意力集中在呼吸上
Mal?
Sweetheart?
宝贝?
It's okay.
没事了
In the auction business,they have an expression
在拍卖行业 有一个术语
called "the halo effect."
称为"光晕效应"
You know what that is?
你知道那是什么吗?
It's when an object or work of art is more desirable
就是 一件物品或艺术品
because of its prior ownership.
会因为它原先的主人而更有价值
Very rare when it happens, you know? Maybe once in a lifetime.
这种事情很少见 你懂吗? 可能一生仅一次
Gotta catch it when you can.
不要浪费了这大好的机会呀
Look, I got plenty of drama in my own office.
看 我自己工作上就够乱的了
You were his contact.
你是他的线人
No, I was his employer.
不 我曾是他的老板
There's a very big difference, trust me.
二者截然不同 相信我
There's only one person I trust.
我只相信一个人
Your dad, yes. He okay?
你父亲 好吧 他还好吗?
He's fine. Thanks for cleaning up.
很好 多谢你清理干净现场
Well, I told you you can have Kenneth alone at the house. I promised you that.
嗯 我告诉过你你有机会和Kenneth一对一的 我对你承诺过
It should at least make me a colleague,
如果做不了朋友的话
if not a friend.
这点应该至少能让我们成为同事
And if something happens to you?
那如果你遇到不测？
Well, then you're screwed.
嗯 那你就完蛋了
One friend's not a lot.
一个朋友不算多
It depends on who it is.
那要看是谁了
- And the kid who helped me?  - We'll fix the ding in his car.
- 那么那个帮过我的孩子呢?  - 我们会修好他的车的
Okay, I will buy him a new car.
好吧 我会给他买辆新车
What is that, an incentive?
这算什么 奖励吗?
It could be.
算是吧
You gotta admit
你必须承认
that this type of life appeals to a certain kind of person.
这种生活方式对某类人是很有吸引力恶
You know? You're off the grid,you never answer to anybody.
你懂吗? 远离喧嚣 不再听命于任何人
Always looking over your shoulder.
时时刻刻小心谨慎
And you got Kenneth out there with all his contacts.
而且你让Kenneth逃了出来 和他众多的党羽一起
Makes you pretty vulnerable.
你现在的处境应该很危险
Where is he?
他在哪?
Well, Mallory, that is a valuable piece of information, isn't it?
Mallory 这是条很宝贵的信息 不是吗?
We think he's crossed the border.
我们认为他已经越过边境了
Possible sightings in Veracruz.
可能在维拉克鲁斯(墨西哥城市)观光呢
But what would be nice to know is what he gave everything up for.
但是 我们很高兴弄清楚了 是什么让他放弃一切逃走
So we're back to the government option.
所以我们又要替政府干活了
Pays less, taxes are taken out.
报酬更少 扣除税收
But you get your good name back.
但可以洗清你的罪名
I'll let you know.
我会答复你
- When?  - When I have him.
- 什么时候?  - 等我抓到他
Yes?
你好?
Kenneth.
Kenneth
He's not available.
他没空
I'm good.
没事
Just going for a walk.
去散散步
Fuck!
妈的
Who did I extract in Barcelona?
我在巴塞罗那救的是谁
You mean who did you kill in Dublin?
你是说那个你在都柏林杀掉的人吗?
Tide's coming in.
要涨潮了
It was a journalist, a dissident.
他曾是位记者 一个持不同政见的人
A dissident journalist, a scientist, what does it matter?
一个持不同政见的记者 一个科学家 有什么关系?
It mattered to someone. Who?
关系到某人 他是谁?
You were excited on the phone. What do you have?
你刚在电话里好像很激动 怎么了？
A unique alignment of conditions.
独一无二大好时机
I know this man, Jiang, has been a problem for you,
你认识Jiang吧 他一直是你的眼中钉
Leaking information and so forth.
泄露机密等等
Restricting your movements.
约束你的行为
I also know this Kane girl is about to leave her employer
我也了解到有个叫Kane女孩打算离开她的雇佣者
and take all his business with her.
而且会带走他所有的生意
Which he won't survive.
以至他无法生存
So when I get word that
所以当我得到消息说
Jiang has been staying in a safe house in Barcelona,
Jiang 住在巴塞罗那的藏身处时
I see an opportunity for everyone
我知道大家的机会来了
to transcend their circumstances.
打破困局的机会
You mean hire the girl to rescue Jiang?
你的意思是雇佣这个女孩救Jiang?
And I deliver him to you.
然后我把他转交给你
The story will be that she's gone rogue.
就说她背叛了组织
Sold out on the Barcelona job
在巴塞罗那那次行动中被出卖
and murdered a man for money at Russborough.
而且为了钱在Russborough杀了一个男人
Resistance?
他反抗呢？
He won't be in a position to.
他没有机会的
Put a bullet in him,
给他一枪
plant the broach on him, and then kill her when you get back to the hotel.
再给他一刀 然后会酒店杀了她
- Self-defense.  - Of course.
- 正当防卫  - 当然
I'm assuming the motive of everyone involved is strictly professional?
我可以假设所有参与行动的人员的动机都是职业性的吗?
Paul, the motive is money.
Paul 动机是钱
The motive is always money.
至始至终动机都是钱
What about Kenneth? Can he guarantee delivery?
Kenneth怎么样?  他能担保交付吗?
It's a two-for-one deal.
这可是一箭双雕之计
You take Jiang out,
你除掉Jiang
Kenneth takes the Kane girl out.
Kenneth除掉kane
To close the loop.
圆满结束
With no one looking.
天衣无缝
Yeah. You're right.
嗯 你是对的
She does sound perfect.
她听起来很完美
You only have to look at her.
你看着她就知道了
What about the girl?
那个女孩怎么样?
- What about her?  - Can she handle herself?
- 她怎么了?  - 她能处理好自己吗?
I'm sure you'll cope.
我相信你会处理
I've never done a woman before.
我从未杀过女人
You shouldn't think of her as being a woman.
你不要因为她是女人而大意
No, that would be a mistake.
真的 不要抱有那种想法
What's in this for you?
你能从中得到什么?
Besides my money.
除了我的报酬外
A new life.
一个新的人生
And a new wife.
和一位新的夫人
That's everything I know.
这就是我所知道的一切
That's everything I know. That's it.
我知道的 就这些
Mallory!
现在起 你只能吃一颗草莓
好恐怖噢
但我不确定你
配不配吃
还要吗
轮到你了
我 为什么是我
- 轮到你了 - 吃了它
坏死了
坏
Dianna.
Dianna
告诉他们茶里别放糖
别把冰弄碎了
Dianna.
Dianna
Shit.
该死
--==圣城家园SCG字幕组 http://hd.cnscg.com/==--
协调：心仪Sally
翻译: 死神夜月 RK翔  hangubing
校对：心仪Sally